Are you nervous?
緊張してるかな?
Do you ever talk like this in front of the camera?
カメラの前でこうやってお話することとかあったりするかな?
No.
ないです
Is there not?
ないかな?
It's cute.
かわいいね
Has anything good happened recently?
最近なんかいいこととかあった?
do not have.
ない
What do you do on your days off?
休みの日とか何してるの?
Shopping.
お買い物
Shopping?
お買い物?
What are you going to buy?
何買うの?
Just looking.
見てるだけ
Are you just looking?
見てるだけ?
What are you watching?
何見てるの?
Clothes?
お洋服?
Yeah.
うん
I like clothes.
お洋服好きなんだ
It's fashionable, what you're wearing today.
おしゃれだよね、今日の格好
It's cute.
かわいいね
How tall are you?
身長とかいくつくらいなの?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Hey.
ねえ
It's cute.
かわいいね
What type of man do you like?
好きな男性のタイプとか?
A mature person.
大人っぽい人
That's right.
そうなんだ
What about celebrities?
芸能人とかは?
Should I watch YouTube?
YouTubeとか見るかな?
I don't see it.
見ない
Don't you see it?
見ないの?
Hey, we just went to a coffee shop together.
ねえ、さっきさ、一緒にさ、喫茶店入ったじゃん
It's a bit difficult to speak in front of the camera.
ちょっとさ、やっぱカメラの前だとちょっとやっぱ喋りづらいで
Sho?
しょ?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, let's talk to my uncle for a moment.
じゃ、 ちょっとおじさんとお話ししていこうか
Well then, how old are you now?
じゃあさ、今さ、年齢とかいくつ?
You wouldn't be able to go to Mizusakaya if it was like this.
水坂屋さんとか行けないでしょ、このだけの感じだったら
Have you ever been able to stay overnight for karaoke?
カラオケとかでも泊められたりすることある?
do not have.
ない
Is school fun?
学校楽しい?
Yeah, it's fun.
うん、楽しい
It's fun.
楽しいんだ
Do you have a favorite subject?
好きな教科とかはある?
do not have?
ない?
Hmm, music.
う ーん、音楽
I love music.
音楽好きなんだ
Sounds like a good song.
なんか歌とかうまそうだね
It's cute.
かわいいね
School is fun.
学校楽しいんだ
Do you meet someone you like?
好きな人とかいたりするの?
not present.
いない
Isn't it?
ないでしょ?
not present.
いない
He's not there.
いないんだ
What about your boyfriend?
彼氏さんは?
There is.
いる
いるんだ
Where did you meet that?
それはどこで出会ったの?
Which one is cooler, me or you?
俺とどっちかっこいい?
boyfriend.
彼氏
I thought I'd give you some money for it.
それによってお金あげちゃおうと思っちゃった、
now.
今
Hey, it's nice to see you smile.
ちょっとね、笑顔見えてよかったよかった
Now, you've given me permission to take pictures.
さあ、撮影OKしてくれたじゃん
Why did you give me the OK?
なんでOKしてくれたの?
Hmm, I want to buy a big one.
う ーん、大きく買いたいし
Because my boyfriend's birthday is coming up.
彼氏の誕生日が近いから
I'll give you a present.
プレゼントしてあげるんだ
You need money.
お金必要だよね
Uncle, it's a bit of an appearance,
おじさんね、ちょっと見た目的にね、
You're fat, right?
太ってるでしょ?
I have a lot of money.
いっぱいお金持ってるよ
Because I'm eating good food.
いいもの食べてるから
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
This is it.
これね
Personally.
個人でね
I shoot things that I enjoy.
俺が楽しむもので撮ってるから
Because it's okay.
大丈夫だから
Can I get a peace?
ピースとかもらってもいい?
That's a great piece.
すごいピースだね
I'm still nervous, after all.
まだ緊張してるんだ、やっぱり
What do you think?
どうだ、どうどうどう?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Can I ask you naughty questions?
エッチな質問とかしていい?
Do you like sex?
エッチ好き?
I've never been there before.
あんましたことない
Which one is S or M data?
SとMデータどっちかな?
What about M?
Mは?
M
teeth.
は
Do you take notes or anything?
メ モなりとかしたりするの?
Hmm, not really.
うーん、あんまり
Oh, I'll do it.
あ、するんだ
Well, I've done it before.
じゃあ、したことあるんだ
Do you use toys or anything?
おもちゃとか使ったりするの?
Well, sometimes.
うーん、たまに
It's surprisingly naughty.
意外にエッチなんだね
Well then, it's school now.
じゃあさ、今、学校じゃん、
now.
今
Because it's a quiz.
ク イズだから
Do you like penis?
おちんちん好き?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいんだ?
So, is it okay if I go next door for a while?
じゃあ、ちょっと隣行っても平気?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
Are you standing all the time?
ずっと立ってるの?
Well, you can just stand there, and then I'll stick my head up for a moment.
じゃあ、立ったままでいいから、じゃあちょっと頭のでさして
Don't hate me like that.
そんな嫌がんないでよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
Look this way, look this way.
こっち向いて、こっち向いて
Please, please, come this way.
お願い、お願い、こっち向いて
I'm nervous, so I'll give you a massage.
緊張してるから、じゃあマッサージしてあげるよ
Don't you hate it when I don't pat your head?
頭撫でないの嫌いじゃない?
This way.
こっちとさ
Look, it's an old man.
見て、おじいさんね
Look, look, look.
見て、見て、ほら
Did I become like this when I patted you on the head?
頭撫でてこんなになっちゃった?
What's going on with this?
これどうなってる?
I made it big.
大きくしちゃった
You made it big.
大きくしちゃったね
good?
いい?
Let's take a commemorative photo with my uncle.
ちょっとおじさんと一緒に記念撮影でもしようか
Peace, peace
ピ ースして、ピース
do.
して
It's so small.
ち っちゃいね
Would you like to compare?
比べてごらん?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
what up?
どうした?
It smells amazing.
すごいいい匂いするよ
cute.
かわいい
Come here.
こっち来て
Well, there is a difference between children and adults.
ね、子供と大人くらい差があるね
Look here?
こっち見てごらん?
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Can I have a chew?
チューしていい?
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
why?
なんで?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Well then, please take a look at me.
じゃあ 俺チューしてよ
Do you hate it?
嫌いのかい?
Cheeks, cheeks.
ほっぺ、ほっぺ
Wouldn't it be nice if it were cheeks?
ほっぺだったらいいでしょ?
Can I chew it on your cheek?
ほっぺにチューさせていい?
Do mine too, cheeks.
俺のもして、ほっぺ
Wouldn't it be nice if it were cheeks?
ほっぺだったらいいでしょ?
It's okay, it's okay.
いいから、いいから
Chew.
チューって
It's cute.
かわいいじゃん
Look this way.
こっち向いて
But kissing is normal overseas.
でも海外だったらキスって普通だから
Why don't you give it a try?
ちょっとチューってしてみよ?
Looking at the camera.
カメラを目線で
Do you know about kissing using the tongue?
舌使うキスとかわかる?
And I'll smell it again
そしてまた匂い嗅ぐよ?
I don't like it.
嫌ー
Okay then, right?
じゃあいいでしょ?
Chew.
チューして
Give me a flyer.
ビラ出して
The flyer is soft.
ビラ柔らかいね
Which curry was better?
カレーさんのどっちがうまかった?
Just try again.
ちょっともう一回やって
Which one was better?
どっちがうまかった?
I won't say it.
言わない
Won't you say it?
言わない?
It's cute.
かわいいね
Chew.
チューして
Serve it and try to make a piece while looking at the camera.
したべーって出して、カメラ目線でピースしてみて
Look this way.
こっち向いて
What do you say here?
ここなんて言うの?
Is that the part you don't like?
嫌って言う部分なの?
What a crazy thing to say.
なんて言うとけてこな
Do you like having your breasts protected?
おっぱい守られたりするの好き?
Don't you hate it?
嫌いじゃない?
Human hair is so cute.
人毛かわいいじゃん
Show me, show me.
見 せて見せて
I can't see it.
見えないよ
Looking at the camera while facing this way.
こっち向きつつカメラ目線で
Is there a lot of human hair this color?
こういう色の人毛が多いの?
What color does your mother use?
お 母さんどんな色使う?
pink.
ピンク
I like pink.
ピンク好きなんだ
Yeah.
うん
I don't like it.
嫌
嫌だ
Please be heard.
お願い聞いてもらってもらう
Have them eat.
食べてもらう
Look right at me.
ちゃんとこっち向いて
Open your eyes properly.
ちゃんと目開けて
I'm chewing on that.
噛んでるよ、それ
It's smooth, it's red.
すべすべだね、赤いから
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Look at my house with these feet.
この足でさ、俺のお家見て
Make your legs.
足作って
I could still see it at a glance.
パッとまだ見えたね
Then sit down for a moment in the morning.
じゃあちょっと朝目に座って
Have your legs spread.
足 開いてもらう
Open your legs.
足開いて
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
I don't like it.
嫌
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
Open your legs.
足開いて
I'll have you sit down right away.
早速座ってもらうじゃん
You don't like it, right?
嫌だろ?
Sorry, I like it when you hate uncles.
ごめん、おじさん嫌ってあるのが好きなんだけどね
Yeah
うん
Yeah yeah.
うん うん
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
No, look.
いや、ほら
I'll never do anything that stands up for me.
立ってくれたものは今までやらないから
It's red after all.
やっぱり赤いね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいんだ?
Look.
ほら
cute.
可愛い
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
So let's say yay and peace together.
じゃあ、一緒にイェーイってピースしよう
Yay.
イ ェーイ
It's cute.
可愛いじゃん
Yay.
イェーイ
I don't like it.
嫌ー
3 seconds?
3秒か
One more time.
もう 一回
I don't like it!
嫌!
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌なんだ
Because I don't like it, I won't do it anymore.
嫌もうやらないから
Okay, I'll vouch for it again.
よし、また腰保証するよ
I don't like it.
嫌
Your breasts are beautifully shaped.
おっぱい形きれいじゃん
Now, face the camera.
さあ、カメラにさあ、顔向けて
Is it visible?
映ってる?
face.
顔
Look, look.
見て、ほら
I don't like it.
嫌
It's slimy, you see.
ぬるぬるしてるよ、ほら
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I want you to spread it out like this and apply it from below.
こうやって広げて、下からかかれてほしい
Have you ever done a pose like this?
こんなポーズしたことある?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I want you to ask me to look at my pussy.
私のマンコ見てくださいって言ってほしいんだよね
Please look at my pussy.
私のマンコ見てください
And I'm fine.
で、私大丈夫だよ